<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wrist Tweets plugin</string>
    <!-- 
    	The following strings needs to be defined in order for the Plugin to function.
    -->
    <string name="pluginname">Wrist Tweets plugin</string>
    <string name="intent_preferences">com.sonyericsson.extras.liveview.plugins.wristtweets.PREFERENCES</string>
    <string name="intent_service">com.sonyericsson.extras.liveview.plugins.wristtweets.WristTweetsService</string>
    <string name="application_description">Wrist Tweets, a Twitter notification plug-in for Sony Ericsson notifiers.\nFor: LiveView\nExtends:com.sonyericsson.extras.liveview</string>
<string name="about">About Wrist Tweets</string>
<string name="about_text">Wrist Tweets is a Twitter(tm) notification app for the Sony LiveView(tm).\n\n

                          Wrist Tweets does it\'s best to be a reliable Twitter notification app. 
                          It can monitor your timeline, mentions/@replies, direct messages, a Twitter list and will notify you of updates.
                          Just enter the username, and optionally the name of the list you want to monitor\n
                          Authentication is done using OAuth, so your password is never stored locally.\n
                          By default, Wrist Tweets is smart about opening URLs and will open the first URL in 
                          a tweet when you press the LiveView action button, rather than just 
                          forwarding to the Twitter page.\n
                          The Sony LiveView(tm) is innovative but buggy, and will often disconnect. 
                          This plugin can be set to check for updates each time the LiveView is 
                          reconnected - this way you are less likely to miss notifications.
                          \n\n
                          About Twitter permissions: Although this app is only for receiving and not sending tweets,
                           it requires Twitters \"Read, Write and Access direct messages\" permission. This is purely so 
                           it can notify you of direct messages. Unfortunately, Twitters new permissions model 
                           (as of ~June 2011) does not have an option to Read tweets (including direct messages) 
                           without also allowing the app to Write (eg Post tweets). So while WristTweet must 
                           request this permission, it will never post a tweet or mess with your follower list.
                          \n\n
                          Legal:\n
                          Wrist Tweets is available under the MIT license at http://github.com/omgwtfgames/wrist-tweets.
                          This software uses JTwitter (http://www.winterwell.com/software/jtwitter.php) which is licenced under the LGPL (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl.html) by Winterwell Associates 2008/2009 and ThinkTank Mathematics Ltd, 2007. 
                          It also uses the Signpost OAuth library (http://code.google.com/p/oauth-signpost/) under the Apache License, version 2.0, since that\'s what JTwitter likes to use.
                          It also uses some MIT licensed open source code written by Sony Ericsson as part of the LiveView SDK - kudos to Sony for opening up to third party developers. Keep up the good work !
                          \n\n\n
                          Wrist Tweets is copyright Andrew Perry, 2011, 2012.\n 
                          http://omgwtfgames.com/category/wrist-tweets-plugin \n</string>
</resources>
